[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements regarding the mathematical constant, pi, is incorrect?", "correct_answer": "There is no zero in the decimal expansion of pi", "incorrect_answers": ["In September of 2002, Dr. Yasumasa Kanada at Tokyo University calculated pi to 1.2411trillion decimal places", "22/7 is a good approximation for the value of pi", "The first written reference to the ratio of a circles circumference to its diameter was written about 1650 b.c.e"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cupid, named after a character in a Shakespearean play and discovered in 2003 with the help of the Hubble telescope, is a small natural satellite of which planet?", "correct_answer": "Uranus", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Saturn", "Neptune"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Major Max Armbruster was played by George Kennedy in the The Dirty Dozen war drama.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The planet of this sign is Uranus. The most recognizable feature of people born under the sign is their need for independence. They are positive and optimistic, and see life as a wonderful adventure.", "correct_answer": "Aquarius", "incorrect_answers": ["Libra", "Gemini", "Pisces"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "More and more people are choosing replacement therapies with human growth hormones. What are the effects of such therapies on the body?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Less body fat", "Stronger immune system", "Younger skin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the animal featured in the insignia of the Apollo 11 mission, the first mission to land a human being on the Moon?", "correct_answer": "An eagle", "incorrect_answers": ["A hawk", "A bear", "A lion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is not a cause of the medical problem, Pink eye?", "correct_answer": "chlorine", "incorrect_answers": ["virus infection", "seasonal pollens", "bacteria pneumococci"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the Edgar Allen Poe House in Baltimore supposedly haunted by the ghost of the eponymous author?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following doctors is least likely to ever be on call?", "correct_answer": "Emergency Physician", "incorrect_answers": ["General Surgeon", "Anesthesiologist", "Family Practitioner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sundance Kid is better at shooting when hes moving.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Jennifer Anistons character in the 2005 comedy movie Rumor Has It...?", "correct_answer": "Sarah", "incorrect_answers": ["Rita", "Annie", "Molly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the largest group of Greek islands?", "correct_answer": "The Cyclades", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sporades", "The Ionian", "The East Aegean"]}]